Guide to the Glenn Sitzman papers, 1940-2010.
Sitzman, Glenn papers, 1940-2010
- Series I. Personal and Professional Papers
  - Clinton High School diploma (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Clarion University Emeritus Faculty certificate (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Around the World - General correspondence, tickets, etc., 1971 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Around the World - Africa, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Around the World - India and Indonesia, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Around the World - Philippines, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Around the World - Japan, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Travel Memorabilia - Philippines and Japan, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Travel Memorabilia - Japan, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 7-8)
  - Travel Memorabilia, 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Travel Memorabilia - Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence re Sabbatical, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - West Africa, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Central Africa, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - East Africa, 1980-1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - African invitations [also some U.K. 1971], 1964-1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Federal Nigeria, 1964, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - British Guiana - Michael Swan (book), 1957 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Colantuono, Louis A. (boylover) - prison correspondence, 1981-1987 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - Pan - articles by or about Colantuono, 1984, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Pan and other publications: Duhahz, Casimir, The Asbestos Diary, 1982; Panthology Three, 1984; Colantuono, Louis A., The Trucker and the Teens, 1984, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Colantuono, Louis A.; The Trucker and the Teens, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Emerick, Kenneth Fred, correspondence, 2004 (Box 10)
  - Emerick, Kenneth Fred, War Resisters Canada (inscribed by the author), 1972 (Box 10)
  - Articles, photographs, etc. relating to the book, 1972-1978 (Box 10)
  - Curata, Ito M. - artwork (Folder 1)
  - Reese, Sammy - artwork (Folder 2)
  - Reese, Sammy - Ricardo R. Carter - drawing, sketch of Jack Branyon (Folder 3)
  - Puerto Rican Library Association posters (Folder 4)
  - Travel Memorabilia - Japan (Folder 5)
  - Broadsides and Posters
    - Philippines: Gen. Makabulos 100th year (Folder 6)
    - Drug abuse (2 items) (Folder 6)
    - Family planning; Agriculture (Folder 6)
    - Philippines-Japan Highway (Folder 6)
    - New constitution & economy (Folder 6)
    - Clean-up campaign; "Read to Lead" (Folder 6)
    - Nigeria (Folder 6)
    - Currency reform, 1965 (Folder 6)
    - Currency reform, 1973 (2) (Folder 6)
    - Theater poster & program - "Day of Sasswood," 1965 (Folder 6)
    - Puerto Rico - travel posters (Folder 6)
- Series II. Family Papers - Genealogy
  - Genealogy - General, 1973-1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Germans in America, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Farnes, Jim, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Germans in Russia (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - American Historical Society of Germans from Russia, 1975-1995 (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
  - Genealogy unrelated to G. L. S. family history (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Genealogy - Eckhardts (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Eckhardt, Hilde (Mrs. Albert) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Hurst, Florine (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Magalis, Alice Wacker (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Patterson, Marian Rolver (daughter of Clara Eckhardt) (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Eckhardt article, related material (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Clausen, Barbara (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Evans, Doris Eckhardt (Box 23, Folder 9-13)
  - Genealogy and family photo album, 1891-195? (Box 42)
  - Amen, Delbert, 2002-2005 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Amos, Geraldine Odester, 2002-2004 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Baker, Don, 2000-2005 (Box 47, Folder 3-4)
  - Carr, Kathryn P. (Penn), 2002-2004 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Coluccio, Roelie, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Cotto, Orlando, 1964-2005 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Curry, Ty, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Danchi, Higashi, 2005-2006 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Debus, Sylvia, 2002-2006 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Evans, Bill & Doris, 2002-2004 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Fellows, Will, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Fitzgibbon, Henry, 19---2003 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Freiband, Susan, 2003-2009 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Frivoll, Anne F., 1967-2005 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Gamaluddin, Connie, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Holloway, Dr. Ernest L., 1999-2003 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Howerton, William, 2005-2008 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Igwe, Ben, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Johnston, James, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Katayama, Takatoshi, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Magalis, Alice W., 2003-2004 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Maloney, Mary, 2007-2009 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Mohamedali, O. N., 2001-2006 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Neitz, Cordelia M., 2001 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Nitecki, Andre, 2003-2004 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Nyarko, George, 1991-1992 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Owobowale, Timi, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Parker, Richard K., 2005-2006 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Patterson, Marian D., 2002 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Plumbe, Wilfred J., 2001-2005 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Seligman, Frances M., 2009 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Shelley, Lee, 2003-2005 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Stephens, Donald, 2000, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Stiles, Julie, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Takeuchi, Satoru, 2001-2006 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Takeuchi, Satoru - 2 books by, 1974, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Villalobos-Concepcion, José Angel, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Ware, Donald and William Howerton, 2003-2004 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - Wilkinson, E., 2000-2004 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Williams, Lee H., 2002-2006 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - Edna, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - Christmas greetings and Valentine, 2005-2006 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - Artworks by men in prison (Box 55)
  - Photo album (Box 56)
  - Newspapers re hurricanes, 2004 (Box 57)
  - Genealogy - Adlers, 1992, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - AHSGR, 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - AHSGR, 2000-2001 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - AHSGR, 2002, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - AHSGR, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Brungardts (genealogy), 1974-1992 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Brunnental Village Newsletter (genealogy), 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Eckhardts (genealogy), 1992, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Eckhardts (genealogy), 1994 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Eckhardts (Lydia Sitzman Eckhardt) (genealogy), 1944-1988 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Genealogy - Eckhardt, Hartung/Hardung, Heimbigner, Urhich, Amen, Gettman, Herbst, Bauer (genealogy), 1995 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Genealogy - Frank, Russia (genealogy), 1995 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Genealogy - The Village Frank Newsletter (genealogy), 1986-1992 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Genealogy - The Village Frank Newsletter (genealogy, 1992-1996 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Genealogy - Frank Newsletter correspondence (genealogy), 1985-1998 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Genealogy - Die Huckere (newsletters and correspondence) (genealogy), 1996-1998 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Germans in Russia (Box 58)
  - Germans in Russia (Box 59)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Books - cataloged individually in the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections
Calva, Jose Rafael. El Jinete Azul, 1885 (annotated, with photograph)
Calva, Jose Rafael. Utopia Gay, 1983 (inscribed by author, annotated, with photograph)
Calva, Jose Rafael. Variaciones y fuga sobre la Clase Media, 1980 (inscribed by author)
Heron, Ann. One Teenager in 10, 1983 (with letter and photograph)
Revista de Belas artes 1, April 1982
Revista de Belas artes 2, May 1982
Lefcourt, Peter The Dreyfus Affair, 1993 (includes clippings and other baseball memorabilia)
Gay, A. Nolder. The View from the Closet, 1978 (autographed, with letter) [HSX]
Pamphlets - Onitsha pamphlets (erotic literature of a newly- literate society): Mabel the Sweet Honey that Poured Away; Never Trust All That Love You; Beware of Harlots and Many Friends